r6998
- Fix: if min enemy group size is too high, the AI never replensishes garrisons, thereby severely dumbing down the game. - Fix: enemy groups do not receive minimum size - Fix: enemy groups sizes are cut down needlessly
---------------------
r6997
- Campaign stats take spy actions and SAM sabotages into account - spy encounters are not reproted if nothing of interest happened - Fix: error in food system automatic canteen refill
---------------------
r6995
Enemy taunt boxes now appear a bit above a soldier, to not interfere with aiming.
---------------------
r6993
- Bugfix: Changed font for sector loadscreens from FONT12ARIAL to FONT12ARIAL to support more characters (e.g: ')
---------------------
r6989
Bugfix (by Buggler) - Fixed incorrect shipping costs in BobbyR Shipment page - Duplicate laptop webpage hotkeys (e -> Enter, q -> BACKSPACE)
---------------------
r6985
- Fix: battle reports no longer report that a team came from north if it was already in sector. - Fix: red lines at wrong locations
---------------------
r6983
Changed inventory dialog to hotkey Ctrl+[v] (before Ctrl+[i]) (by Sevenfm)
---------------------
r6981
Enabled auto-taking for concertina/sandbags (by Sevenfm) - items are taken from current merc's inventory - works only in realtime - when filling sandbags, filled sandbag is dropped, and new empty is taken from inventory - you need to press ...
---------------------
r6976
- Food system change: if a soldier autofeeds, he will refill his canteens if the sector has drinkable water - do not display corruption backgriund in 1.13 - removed hardcoded direction number
---------------------
r6975
CTRL+LeftClick on an item with an attachment in the hand cursor would attach it without any AP costs. Now the game will deduct the correct attachment AP.
---------------------
r6971
Fix: MERC members accounts not displayed if they were at the end of the list
---------------------
r6970
Merged revision(s) 6969 from trunk/GameSource/ja2_v1.13: Fix: STR stat damage from starvation was not read correctly 
---------------------
r6965
- [CTRL] + [i] in tactical calls a dialogue for sector inventory manipulations (by Sevenfm) - [CTRL] + [c] in tactical calls a dialogue for cover/trap display modes (by Sevenfm) - changed min value for SCOPE_RANGE_MULTIPLIER from 0.5 to 0.1...
---------------------
r6964
Merged revision(s) 6963 from trunk/GameSource/ja2_v1.13: Fix: soldiers without a face index should not use Character Dialogue that uses face index 
---------------------
r6961
- Bugfix: John Kulba (and other NPCs) did not show up on MERC website even if MERC_WEBSITE_ALL_MERC_AVAILABLE  = TRUE (by anv) 
---------------------
r6957
reverted length of loadscreenhints back to 190. 
---------------------
r6953
- Increased text limit for load screen hints from 190 to 254 o Hopefully this does not cause any problems when rendering on the loadscreens. Tests resulted in success - Support for localization of LoadScreenHints.xml (*.LoadScreenHints.xml)...
---------------------
r6949
- Multiplayer: Only output the notification info message about stucking enemy in a CO-OP game!
---------------------
r6948

---------------------
r6946
- Bugfix: Fixed wrong IMP mail result entry for Radio Operator skill
---------------------
r6941
- Map Editor Bugfix: Fixed corruption of gpItem variable in Map Editor Build (by Kriplo)
---------------------
r6939
- Bugfix: Fixed crash (Access violation popup) in Release build (VS2005/2008) when quitting the game (thx Kriplo)
---------------------
r6937
- Added support for language specific *.AttachmentSlots.xml files
---------------------
r6926
- Translated Chinese source code files (by John_5696)
---------------------
r6922
- Bugfix: Localization not working for multiple *.EnemyTaunts_*.xml files
---------------------
r6916
- Fixed compilation error for JA2UB
---------------------
r6912
- Allow reading of language specific *.MercStartingGear.xml Kit names - Fixed *.Pockets.xml not working - Reworked a few German texts
---------------------
r6905
Updated Snitches - Added missing Chinese Texts
---------------------
r6904
Improved Snitch Trait (by anv) - The snitch actions can be selected in the strategy view "Assignment" menu o Spreading Propaganda: Accessible in town sectors o Gathering Rumours: Accessible in town sectors o Undercover Prison Snitch: Access...
---------------------
r6900
- Translated missing Chinese texts (by John_5696)
---------------------
r6898
- Fixed wrong/missing texts
---------------------
r6894
Fixes (by Buggler) - IMPPrejudice page not showing when reviewing in finish mode - Added message when minor traits are unselectable due to all IMP available slots taken up by major traits - Display message when pressing hotkey 'G' to toggle...
---------------------
r6893
fixed Skyrider missing face and sticky dialogue text in strategic map
---------------------
r6889
Brief: //dnl ch85 - Some fixing and adding position in overhead map to be in center of big map. Details: - Calculate overhead map cords from your current position on big maps. - Fix incorrect placing room numbers in maps with cliffs. - Fix ...
---------------------
r6887
Bugfix for number of minor traits (by anv)
---------------------
r6881
- close item description box when autoplace item from sector inventory (by Buggler) - allow toggling of item restriction only when move item button is activated (by Buggler) - sector inventory item filter buttons now shows in 640x480 too (b...
---------------------
r6879
Editor fixes (by Buggler): - fixed incorrect item display after deleting map-placed item in stack - revert r5949 code for item deletion from item pool
---------------------
r6877
Minor improvement/fix for "Improved Bomb Planting" feature. (by Sevenfm) 1. Now you don't need to hold shift all the time while planting bomb, just shift+click is enough. 2. If successfully taken new bomb from inventory (or using Tripwire R...
---------------------
r6871
- updated NCTH targeting optics in Interface.cpp to use the same order and formulas as LOS.cpp. It's easier to read and compare this way. - added scope effectiveness which defines the maximum magnification bonus a shooter can get using scop...
---------------------
r6868
Brief: //dnl ch84 - Solve issues related to my recent editor fixes. Details: - Fix missing condition when using keyboard for load any map from listed profiles in CTRL+L list box. - Fix CTD during gWorldItems resize after adding certain amou...
---------------------
r6862
Fix for AI opponent finding
---------------------
r6856
Fix for AI CTH evaluation with NCTH
---------------------
r6853
- Fix: with a very large team in dire circumstances, accumulated snitch events corrupted memory - Fix: missing morale event handling (by anv)
---------------------
r6850
- Translated text to French (by hrvg)
---------------------
r6847
- Bugfix: Fixed initialization not working for foreign language *.EnemyTaunts.xml
---------------------
r6846
- Fixed missing text entry in _FrenchText.cpp
---------------------
r6844
- Fixed French texts (by hrvg)
---------------------
r6836
Fix: incorrect gridno calculation
---------------------
r6833
Fix: on certain conditions, gpCurrentTalkingFace gets garbage values assigned. If BOOLEAN fTalking then does get a value > 0, the incorrect face does not get cleaned.
---------------------
r6828
Code improvement: Instead of calling inv.size() repeatedly, just call it once and remember that value
---------------------
r6827
Fix from r6775 is no longer necessary.
---------------------
r6826
Minor code improvements and cleanup
---------------------
r6824
Map Editor Fixes/Improvements (by Buggler) - Better UI feedback after last item deleted from item stack in editor item mode - Improved editor room number increment code. 'Shift + LMB' when drawing room numbers will reuse same room number on...
---------------------
r6822
- Fix: autoresolve battle reports sector wrong - Fix: reports over #255 are not accessible
---------------------
r6820
Fix: unable to load savegame if more than 255 incidents occured
---------------------
r6814
- Fix: HOURS_BETWEEN_STRATEGIC_DECAY was not read from ini (by anv) - Fix: squads exceeding 20 cannot be accessed 
---------------------
r6812
Reworked Sectory actions menu (CTRL + .) (by Sevenfm) - Also added support for 16 medium size buttons dialog. - see: http://www.bears-pit.com/board/ubbthreads.php/topics/329932.html#Post329932 
---------------------
r6804
- Updated French text files (by hrvg)
---------------------
r6802
Merged from revision: 6798 Fix for ammo icon in description box which showed another shifted description box when ammo type was invalid. http://www.ja-galaxy-forum.com/board/ubbthreads.php/topics/328324/Re:_BUGZILLA_report_all_bugs_h.html#P...
---------------------
r6801
Merged from revision: 6797 - Fixed bug with merc swap feature which was introduced with Waldo the mechanic. Faces were swapped incorrectly.
---------------------
r6795
- UB crashing after helicopter crash in new game (junk variables removed) (by anv)
---------------------
r6794
Merged from revision: 6788 Thanks to Flugente, he perform quick fix for overhead map crash after sector is cleared from enemy, but actual problem was created by me in r6744, I overwrite one condition by mistake, so this will fix the real so...
---------------------
r6792
Fixes (by Buggler) - draw NCTH cursor indicator after health bar indicator due to potential overlap (thanks to Sevenfm) - removed IMPROVED_BOMB_PLANTING option, enabled by default - removed AIMED_BURST_ALTERNATE_KEY option, enabled by defau...
---------------------
r6786
Added missing text line in French version - L"Refuel site"
---------------------
r6785
Merged from revision: 6777 - Fix: M.E.R.C. accounting displayed too many mercs per page (page 2 and  following)
---------------------
r6784
Merged from revision: 6776 FixFix: non-merc planted explosives that fire fragments caused crashes. A few functions had to be fixed.
---------------------
r6783
Merged from revision: 6775 Fix: Opening up sector map could cause crashes.
---------------------
r6782
Merged from revision: 6774 - Fixed dropdown menu glitches
---------------------
r6781
Merged from revision: 6773 - Fix: overly long loadscreen hints caused crashes when displayed in log. Maximum loadscreen length is now 190 (was 256).
---------------------
r6767
- Moved hard coded "Next page" button text for Alumni site to language files
---------------------
r6764
Fixes (by Buggler) - fixed hotkey switch weapons AP cost and empty hand swap - adjusted colors for militia equipment item shading - fixed IMP background button states and previous button array list
---------------------
r6761
- Campaign Stats: Externalized hard coded "and" text to language specific text files
---------------------
r6759
- Updated French texts (by hrvg)
---------------------
r6754
- Updated Build Name from "Development Build" to "2014 Beta Build" - Updated Version number and Version Date - Updated build executable names
---------------------
r6749
Created new branch for the official 2014 release - Based on development trunk rev. 6748   https://ja2svn.no-ip.org/source/ja2/trunk/GameSource/ja2_v1.13 - This branch should only contain bugfixes 
---------------------
